greathippo.com 2017-10-14

# Great Hippo!

The Great Hippo Internet site (the "Site", brought to you by Buntai Ltd.) is a platform which allows you to customize your new tab so you can access your favorite sites within a wave of a hand, and also give you the opportunity to sync your mobile device's address book with a desktop app and thereby answer calls and texts from your computer device. These and the Great Hippo Terms of Service ( **"Terms"** ) are the accesses and terms of your use in the site. 

As used in this privacy policy, **"Personal Information"** means information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity such as a name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. Other terms capitalized but not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Service at www.greathippo.com (the **"Terms"** ). 

### Information We Collect

During Great Hippo installation process, you might be asked to log in to your account (it can be Google or Facebook account) in order to generate your user identifier in Great Hippo systems and to personalize your experience while using Great Hippo. We may collect your name, email address, country of origin, and, if you choose, your nickname, telephone number, website, company, and title. Demographic information may be correlated to web usage information collected during your use of the service. In addition, you might provide us with personal identifying information, such as mobile telephone number, when you communicate with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise, or complete a questionnaire, subscription form or a contest entry form. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing and improving our services, delivering targeted content and advertisements that may be of interest to you, and communicating with you. Great Hippo may also give you the opportunity to sync the names, phone numbers and emails from the address book on your mobile device with the computer device on which you chose to install the Great Hippo extension. If you chose to use the mobile book address synchronization service, then this information will be considered as part of your personal information Great Hippo collects. This information will be restored on our servers and every change you make in your address book will reflected automatically on our servers. Great Hippo disclaims any responsibility for people you are texting them and it is your responsibility to inform these factors that their text messages will be restored in our servers. Great Hippo gives you the opportunity to contact us in case one of this factors want to be removed from our servers and we will remove these text messages within 30 days of receipt of your email. When you use Great Hippo Desktop to call or to send Text massage to identified people, a call event or Text message event will be sent to our servers and our servers will display to you the information that we have on our servers on the specific person you called or text. The call/Text event includes certain information about the call, such as the number you call, the time of the call etc. 

### Information Sharing

We do not sell your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information: 

  * As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process.
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. 
  * If Great Hippo is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.
  * We do not record any calls that you make using Great Hippo.

### Use of Information

Great Hippo may use information (whether personal identifying information or not) that we collect about you to: Manage your relationship with us and provide you with customer support. Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content, or products, services or content offered by others. Communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or third parties. Cooperate with legal, criminal or regulatory investigations or proceedings. Manage our business. 

### Linked Content

Certain sections of the site may involve sites which belongs to third parties. Great Hippo is not and shall not be responsible for that, and any use by the user of the sites belonging to third parties is in his sole responsibility. Therefore, Great Hippo will not be responsible for actions that occurred at sites belonging to third parties. Moreover, Great Hippo warns from sites belonging to third parties and offers the user to read carefully the terms of use of those sites. 

### Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us. 

### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by emailing us at: greathippo@yahoo.com
